hotgvibe.com 2009-06-25

# Hot G Vibe :: Best Online Adult Sex Toys Store - Shop For Male & Female Sex Toys - Vibrating Cock Rings - Penis Extenders - Male Enhancement Pills

### Hot G Vibe Privacy / Security Policy

Terms and Conditions  
[Updated November 28, 2007]

#### Introduction To Our Privacy/Security Policy 

Hot G Vibe wants to help you make the most of your visit to our websites, and that incorporates helping safeguarding your individual privacy. All of the features on our websites are presented without gathering any personal information from you. You can browse the Hot G Vibe websites and view all of our content anonymously. Only when you purchase a product from Hot G Vibe do we require your personal information to process accurately your transaction.

By using this website, you are consenting to the terms of this Hot G Vibe Privacy Policy, as presented in this area of the website. If you do not agree with any terms or practices described in this Privacy Policy, please exit our websites.

As used in this Hot G Vibe Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means personally identifiable information, such as your full name, home address, telephone number, date of birth and e-mail address. When personal information is collected, you will know because you will have to fill out an electronic form on the website. When you make a purchase we will also collect your credit card information as additional personal information. We will use credit card information only to complete the transactions you have requested.

#### Privacy Information

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us. Hot G Vibe will never trade, lease or sell your personnel information that is obtained on this website. We will contact you only if your order/shipping information is incomplete or incorrect.

Hot G Vibe collects Personal Information from visitors to our websites in the following ways: 

  * Purchases of merchandise on our website. 
  * Participation in contests or events. 
  * E-mail transmitted via various links on our web sites. 

Using state-of-the-art encryption security technology, your online order is secure. When you place your order, you will be taken to our secure server prior to being asked for your credit card number. We use an address verification system to compare your billing address to your credit card on file with your bank.

If you send us an e-mail, you should know that e-mail is not necessarily 100% secure against internet fraud. If your communication needs to include sensitive information like your bank account, credit card, or social security number, please contact us by postal mail or telephone (see our contact information below) rather than e-mail.

#### Cookies

In order to track your use of the site, "cookies" may be employed. Cookies are pieces of digital information that are sent by websites and stored in your computer's hard drive, which provide you a service by allowing us to recognize your computer to save you from having to re-enter the same data every time you visit our websites. They also allow us to gain knowledge of how visitors use our websites. This user data is amassed for internet tracking purposes mainly by adding all the pages viewed throughout our websites and logging Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses and browser types. 

If you do not want to receive cookies, you may set your internet browser to reject them. 

#### Visitors From Outside Canada

All personal information collected at our websites is put together and stored in Canada. By submitting personal information to this website, you are consenting to the storage of your personal information in Canada.

#### How We Use Your Information

Hot G Vibe controls the way in which your personal information is used. We use personal information to provide you the products you want, to better comprehend the needs of the Hot G Vibe purchaser. 

If you order our product from us or register for one of our contests, promotions, Hot G Vibe may share personal information with service providers, suppliers and other third parties (for example, sweepstakes sponsors or delivery services). When we share your personal information with third parties, they may use your personal information to send you information on their additional products or services, but Hot G Vibe does not allow them to sell or transfer your personal information to others. We do not otherwise sell or provide your personal information to third parties. 

#### Feedback Information

All feedback provided on this website is regarded to be non-confidential. Hot G Vibe shall be liberated to use such information unrestrictedly.

#### Changes in This Privacy Policy

Hot G Vibe reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here and we will change the “Last Updated” date at the top of this page. We encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay up to date.

#### Contact Us

Any comments or questions about the Hot G Vibe Privacy Policy, can be submitted by e-mail by clicking here.

You may also contact at us by postal mail: 

### Hot G Vibe

5890 Monkland Ave Suite 406  
Montreal, Quebec   
H4A 1G2 CANADA

The information contained in this website is subject to change without notice.

Copyright © 2007 Hot G Vibe  
All rights reserved.
